This video is sponsored by Hansen.
Around the year 2016, I was a
disaffected gamer bro. I considered
myself to be a classical liberal. I
hated those cringe feminists who I
thought were trying to ruin video games,
turn women into gender ambiguous zer
pronoun weirdos, and who waged a war on
sexual attractiveness. I laughed at Big
Red. I laughed at Triglypuff. And I
laughed at Humongous.
>> Domestic duties, over professional
goals, plus minimizing
our traditional marriages.
I'm reading Facebook.
>> You want my name?
>> Yeah, sure.
>> It's humongous.
>> Humongous.
>> Okay.
>> Humongous. What?
>> He said humongous.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. This person just sexually harassed
me.
>> Yes. Yeah, that's right. Fast forward to
2025 and most of those classical [music]
liberal types I used to listen to have
become white nationalists. I, on the
other hand, have chosen a different path
and became dark. What does that entail?
Well, I'm a progressive. I am pro-LGBT.
I am pro- feminism. And I laugh at Big
Red. I laugh at Triglypuff. And I laugh
at Humongous.
>> Are you going to do ANYTHING ABOUT HOW
YOU SEXUALLY HARASS ME?
>> WHY? Because they are completely
ridiculous. Um, Adam, you're being uh
problematic. Shut up. If you don't want
people laughing at you, stop acting like
a fool in front of cameras at highly
publicized events, especially if there
is a whole ecosystem of people out there
who are savvy at making memes and have a
hate boner for you and are just waiting
to clip you. Case in point, if Big Red
had said the exact same things that she
did, but in a friendly and agreeable
tone, she would never have become the
mascot of an anti-feminist online hate
movement. So anyway, I gradually broke
up from the alt-right over time. But the
area of my life where I took the longest
to do so was dating. See, I wanted to
date women. But how do I do it? It was a
mystery to me. By that time, I was more
often in a relationship than single. But
when I got a girlfriend, it kind of just
happened.
I was doing something which sometimes
worked and sometimes didn't. But I
wanted consistent results. I didn't just
want to sleepwalk through my dating life
and hope to stumble upon someone good.
Oh, no. No. I wanted to know exactly how
dating works so that I can actively find
someone great. Both the left and the
right offer dating advice. And so I
first asked around the in lefty circles,
"Hey, how do I score a good girlfriend?"
Um, actually, the term scored is deeply
problematic because it presupposes that
the woman is just an object. Okay, okay,
fine. Forget I said anything. Meanwhile,
on the right, dating advice was
essentially variations on Andrew Tate
type boomer conservative BS, which I was
just not there for. You know, stuff like
you have to show her who's boss. You
have to dominate her. Women are meant to
receive you and submit to you, and so
you must be the one who lords over them
as a man. Never show your feelings.
Never share your fears and anxieties.
You must pay for everything. You must be
the bread winner. You lead, she follows
always. You know that kind of stuff.
Okay, to be fair, there was more to the
left than people just, you know, woke
scolding you about the problematic words
that you're using. Some people did give
you genuine dating advice. Too bad it
was all terrible. Let's look at a
notorious example. But first, let's
shave. But how? Using a razor with 800
blades. No, just kidding. It's
pseudocience. You don't actually need 80
billion blades on your frigin razor. One
is enough as long as it's wellmade. And
Hensen blades are exactly that. Made by
well, Hensson, the sponsor of today's
video. They bank out these blades with
what 0.00002
mm tolerances. That's micron level. And
it actually shows. After shaving, they
went and examined people's skin with a
near infrared spectroscope. And found
that sure enough, high precision single
blades cause far less irritation than
regular cartridge razors. It's nice to
see that they did an actual scientific
investigation rather than entrusting
research onto the marketing department.
Ah yes, more blade equal more good
science. Hensson razors come with a high
build quality. They are just the right
size and weight with excellent blade
stability and balance. This is what
happens when someone actually sits down
to build a proper razor instead of
trying to sell you overengineered crap.
Go to the link in the description and
get yourself a proper Hensen razor
today. Thank you for checking out Hensen
and thanks to Hensen for sponsoring
today's video. All right, so leftist
dating advice. Yeah, check this out. So,
a lonely teenage boy wanting a
girlfriend goes to the left and asks,
"Hello, Mr. Person on the left. How
could I get that hot girl over there to
become my girlfriend?" And Big Joel,
fellow leftist YouTuber, will now give
him some advice. I don't really think
that self-help online advice is all that
helpful to people. Uh, because I think
you already know all the advice that
anybody on the internet could possibly
tell you. young men. Um, do things that
are good in your opinion. Do things that
you think are good. Um, I don't imagine
that I have a better answer for what
those things are than you do. You know,
you know yourself. But, you know, of
course, you know what those things are.
This video is not my way of saying that
all advice on the internet is bad and
that the people who are giving it are
all grifting you [music] and that
there's no place for it. I don't believe
that. I just think it's an extremely
small part [music] of a network with
things that are vastly vastly more
important than it. The amount of impact
that some guy on the internet uh will
have on your life when they give you
advice on how to get motivated or
whatever is I think, you know, fairly
small in the grand scheme of things. And
that's my point. Wow. I'm sorry. I like
Big Joel. I like his videos, but this
type of stuff does not help anyone. It's
like your house is on fire and you're
locked inside with a fire extinguisher
and you're like, "Oh what do I do?
How do I use this thing?" And Joel is
like, "I think you should first consider
that the fire is just a natural
exothermic reaction which will go out at
some point." You know, the fire will
stop at some point. So, I wouldn't
really worry about this long term. I
think you should look inside and figure
out what feels like the best course of
action in this situation. But then
Andrew Day shows up and he's like, "All
right, idiot. Grab the extinguisher.
Pull out the pin. Aim the nozzle at the
fire. Now start making the monkey
sounds. Stand real close to the fire so
that you will sustain at least
secondderee burns. This shall be your
mark of the alpha male. Now press down
the lever and extinguish that fire. Also
remember women are subhuman and Jews run
the world. And this is my big issue with
dating advice on the left. It's not
really advice, just a bunch of useless
platitudes. Be nice, respect women. Go
outside. [music] Work on yourself. Yeah,
great. Thanks. But how do I get the girl
I like to date me? Why are we so afraid
of giving useful practical advice? Like,
can you imagine this in any other
context? Like a young boy goes to their
parents and be like, "Hey, mom, dad,
I've been pretty anxious and depressive
lately. Can you help?" And then the
parents are like, "Well, have you tried
being happy?" Oh, no. If your parents
know what they're doing, they're like,
"All right, son. Are you smoking weed?
Cut that out. Always go to bed at
the same time. Always wake up at the
same time. Structure your day. Go
outside. Meet with your friends. Smell
fresh air. Get some sunlight. Eat
healthy, shower everyday, feel clean,
and always keep your room tidy. [music]
This is good practical advice. On the
other hand, advice like Big Joles is not
really advice. It's more like
inspiration. But young, insecure boys
are not looking for inspiration. They
are not 40some Pinterest wine moms. They
want instructions. What do I do? What do
I not do? How do I succeed? Tell me. And
Andrew Tate and people like him are more
than happy to give them instructions.
very stupid and harmful instructions.
But for many young boys, this is better
than just aimlessly floating down the
river without a rudder, as evidenced by
Tate becoming a globally popular
influencer. Meanwhile, there are good,
healthy, and very useful instructions to
be given to young boys free of all the
farright BS. But it seems like no one on
the left is willing or able to give it
except for one person, me. See, about a
year ago, I have actually put together a
comprehensive dating guide, mostly for
men, but it's genderneutral. I wanted to
have it published as a book, but then I
was like, "Oh, wait. I have a YouTube
channel." I have the guide as a Google
doc about 90 pages [music] long. And in
this video, I'm going to give you the
quick and summarized version. I'll be
simplifying a lot. But if you want the
full comprehensive version, you will
find it right down in the description.
It is completely free. I am not asking
you for any money. Just go and read it.
I hope it will be helpful to you. Oh,
and uh support me on Patreon if you want
to. Also, author's note. If I sound
funny from this point on, that's because
I got co halfway through the recording.
So, there's that. So, all right. dating.
How does it work? How do you get a
girlfriend? I'm going to assume that
you're a guy looking for a girlfriend.
And if you're not, I trust you will fill
in the blanks. So, step one, how does
attraction work? And here I will borrow
an idea from right-wing dating gurus.
They have this attraction scale from 0
to 100, which I think it's a pretty
useful representation tool. On it, 100
is absolute blind love, and zero is
complete and utter indifference. 50 is
the tipping point. Above 50, you're
attracted. Below 50, you're not. When
you see someone, you put them on this
scale. Suppose you're a guy who likes
girls. You see a girl, you put her on
the scale. Like, oh, damn, she's
freaking hot. I literally can't take my
eyes off her. That's like a 90. Oh,
okay. She's cute. That's around 70 or
so. H, fine. 51. Uh, nah, 49. And then
below 49, it's just variations of eh,
not my type. And girls do the same to
you. They look at you and put you on
their own scale. Okay. So, what's needed
on your end for girls to find you
attractive? Meaning 51 or above? Do you
need to be a 2 m tall, 90° square jaw
muing champion ripped gigad with 2% body
fat?
No. Absolutely not. Because attraction
is subjective and unpredictable. Some
girls will just find you attractive for
whatever strange reason. Don't question
it. Don't investigate it. Just be glad
about it. As long as you look healthy,
look clean, and dress okay, some girls
will find you physically attractive, and
that is all you need to start. The girl
doesn't need to be crazy about you from
the start. If you just make it with 51,
so barely passing her bar, that's good
enough. Conversely, if she only barely
passes your bar, that's also good
enough. If a girl is a 51 for you, but
then on dates she turns out to be the
coolest person ever, you'll be in love
with her before you know it. Likewise,
if you are just a 51 for her, but you do
things right and she likes your vibes,
she will also be in love with you soon
enough. So, don't worry. As long as you
both pass each other's bar, have at it.
So, you go and meet girls. And so, out
of 10 girls, maybe three will find you
attractive. So, for them, you're above
50. And out of those three, two will be
in a relationship, so not available. You
are looking for girls who are single and
available for reasons that I hope are
obvious. So, that leaves one girl out of
10, but you don't like her. for you.
She's below 50. Damn. So, zero out of
10. That sucks. But also, that's okay,
dude. Dating is a numbers game. All you
need to do is keep going. Luckily, there
are ways to meet an industrial amount of
women on a budget, so don't worry. So,
meeting girls. If you want to meet
girls, you can do it in real life or
online. If you do it in person, you just
walk up to them and strike up a
conversation. Make sure to have
something in common first. Attending the
same event, doing the same thing, that
sort of stuff. Simply make sure that in
that situation, striking up a
conversation is socially acceptable. So
have a light-hearted conversation and if
you think it goes well, meaning she's
engaged in it, not just yes or no
answers. Then you ask for her phone
number. Hey, it's been fun talking to
you. What's your number? Then once
asking, you shut up. She either gives it
to you or not. If not, she's not
interested. If she does, she is likely
interested. So why the phone? Because
it's more intimate than texting or
social media, yet it is socially
acceptable. You're gauging her interest
here. Do you like me enough to bear the
slight discomfort of giving you my
number? Um, but using the phone is like
super scary. Yeah, shut up, dude. If my
85-year-old grandmother can use the
phone without getting a heart attack,
then so can your Zoomer ass, so I don't
want to hear it. Once you get her
number, say goodbye and leave. No
lingering. It's awkward. And then after
waiting four to 5 days, you call her and
invite her on a coffee date. a half an
hour to hour get together in a safe,
hightraic, neutral place where each of
you will have one or two coffees and try
to feel each other out. Is this person
giving me good vibes? Are they worthy of
a longer more expensive regular date at
a restaurant? And who pays the bill? My
rule of thumb, the person who invites.
You can tell her that if she tries to
pay her way. This is clean, simple,
genderneutral, and socially accepted. If
she wants to pay, she can always invite
you out. Also, why wait four to 5 days
to call? Because every desperate loser
calls her the day of or the next day.
You will be different and show her that
you aren't in fact a desperate loser.
You are in no rush. You take your time.
Just don't wait too long because then
it's insulting. Four or 5 days. Call her
after regular work hours. When calling
her, first have a short about a minute
long light-hearted convo. Then invite
her out. Listen, I'd like to take you
out for coffee. How about x day y time
at z location? Notice how I make it
clear what I want to do and give her the
full package. day, time, place. She has
all the information to make the decision
to accept or not. If she accepts, great.
If not, reschedule it with her. Once you
set the date with her, say, "All right,
thank you. See you then." And then hang
up. Importantly, the phone is only for
setting dates. You will do the talking
on the dates. Don't use up all your
convo topics in advance. This includes
texting. Don't text between dates. Once
you have a date set with her, the next
thing you should do is to show up at the
exact time at the location on that day.
Until then, you have no reason to reach
out to her unless to reschedule or
something like if something super
important comes up for you and you
absolutely have to reschedule. On the
other hand, if she texts you in between
just wanting to talk about some random
stuff, that's great. A sign of interest.
Then just tell her that you can't wait
to discuss all of that on the date.
Okay, so this is all very nice, but what
happens if she doesn't pick up the
phone? If she doesn't pick up, just send
her a text message. Hey, this is your
first name. Please call me back on this
number. Then you write down your number
just in case. If you don't get a call
back, there's your answer. She's not
interested. That means she's out. Look,
I know that sucks. I know that's bad.
But consider this. If she likes you, she
will make it easy for you. There is no
such thing as hard to get. That is just
I'm not interested or mental illness and
you don't care about either. If the girl
genuinely likes you and wants to see
you, you will have an easy time making
dates with her. She will show up. If she
can't make it, she will help you
reschedule. She will make sure that she
will get in front of your face on a
date. All right, this is the gold
standard. Keep this in mind because I
have seen so many guys, including
friends of mine, who are like, um, so
I've been trying to get this single and
available girl on a date for two months
now, but like it's really difficult,
man. It's like, dude, what are you
doing? If she liked you, you would have
an easy time making a date with her. But
you, in fact, are having the opposite of
that. You are having a hard time making
a date with her. And so, what exactly
does that tell you about her interest
towards you? Yeah, right. So, just go
look for someone else. Someone who
actually likes you. All right. So, with
that, let's talk about online dating,
which is very similar. For online
dating, you need photos and maybe a bio.
Your photos will do 99% of the work with
your bio counting for about 1%. On your
photos, you should be clean, smiling,
well-dressed, well lit, doing normal
things, not pushing your face into the
camera, not be a microscopic dot in a
wide-angle panorama shot, and not wear
any sunglasses. People want to see your
eyes. Heavy photo of you in your casual
clothes, formal clothes with some kind
of pet and or you doing your hobby, then
start swiping. On Bumble, Tinder is
utter On Bumble, girls have to
initiate, which is much better for
everyone involved. If you get a match,
have a light-hearted, fun conversation.
After a dozen meaningful messages each,
invite her out on a coffee date.
Definite day, time, and place. If she
declines, like she says she wants to
talk some more, that's fine. A dozen
more meaningful messages each. After
that, if she says no again, she's not
interested. She wants a conversation
partner, not a romantic one. Unmatch.
Next. You won't ask for girls numbers
through dating apps. You do that in
person at the end of the coffee date if
things went well. If they did not go
well, like you weren't feeling it, and
though she turned out to be a huge
idiot, no asking for numbers. Thanks for
coming. It was fun. Goodbye. Unmatch.
Next. The coffee date will be your first
stop almost always. There are some match
cases detailed in the document link
below. Oh, and at the end of the coffee
date, you do not guess. This is just a
vibe check meetup. Don't get ahead of
yourself. So, after the coffee date, you
have her number. The coffee date went
well. She's cute. You both find each
other pleasant. Nice. Wait four to 5
days. Call her and ask her out on a
regular date at a restaurant. Day, time,
place given. Oh, and tell her in advance
that you're going to eat. You don't want
her to show up to dinner with a full
stomach. Oh, and just a quick note. If
during those four to 5 days of waiting,
she reaches out to you for any reason in
any way, that's great. You got incoming.
Use it to set up the next date. If she's
coming at you, you don't wait. The four
to 5 days rule goes out the window. You
set the date. All right. So, on the
date, you sit down, order food, and
talk. Of course, this is all written
about in great detail in the Google doc.
Do check it out below. Don't just rely
on this video. Now, on dates, if both of
you do things right, your feelings for
each other will grow. Both of you will
go up on the scale. If one of you screws
up, that person goes down the scale for
the other. Like, you meet her and she's
super cool and you like her a lot, but
then she's like super rude to the
waiters and it's like, "Oh, well, that
sucks." Now, if you screw up too much,
you risk going below 50. And that, I'm
afraid, is a one-way ticket. Going below
50 means turning off the other person
for good. There is no salvaging that
you're dead. Once the spell is broken,
it's gone forever. Time to look for
someone else and not screw up this time.
Now, what if she dates others beside
you? It can happen and it's completely
okay. And I recommend you do the same.
It balances you out like crazy. And
don't worry, those other guys are
probably clueless. They will fall off
soon enough and you'll be the only one
left if you follow the stuff I wrote in
the book anyway. Okay, so after seven to
eight dates with a girl, if you did
things right, you might start hearing
things like, "Oh, I want to introduce
you to my friends, relatives, etc.
Great. That's boyfriend girlfriend
stuff." You can then innocently nail
things down right there. Oh, that sounds
like something a couple would do. And
then she's like, "Well, I thought we
were." And then you're like, "Well, are
you seeing anyone else beside me?" And
she ideally says, "Nope." Then you say,
"Great. Then we are boyfriend
girlfriend." And then you drop everyone
else you're seeing on the side. Being
boyfriend girlfriend means exclusive.
That means only one person and you will
expect the same from your partner. And
with that, congratulations. You have a
girlfriend at long last. From this
point, it all comes down to relationship
maintenance, which I also detailed in
the Google doc. So, once again, for the
sixth time or something, do check it
out. Especially if you would like to
yell at me over stuff I've said in this
video, go read the doc, see what I meant
in detail. If you still disagree, then
you are free not to apply what I told
you. All right, cool. Thanks. And so I
hope all of this will be helpful to you,
especially if you're a young, lonely guy
who doesn't know how to date. Don't go
to the Insta crowd. Don't go to the
dating gurus. I am giving you everything
you need for success. And I will never
ask you for money for any of it. It's
right there for free. Have fun. Enjoy.
And with that, thank you for watching.
And do check out Hensen, the sponsor of
today's video. Their link is also in the
description. And I'll be seeing you next
time.